{
  "instruction": "For Phase 8 (Portfolio), we need a futuristic 'Command Center' UI. Standard pie charts are boring. Give me 3 wild ideas to visualize 'Asset Allocation' and 'Account Health' (e.g. Health Bars, Holograms). Think Sci-Fi.",
  "results": [
    {
      "model": "opencode/big-pickle",
      "executed": true,
      "output": "Active code page: 65001\n\n\nHere are 3 futuristic sci-fi ideas for visualizing Asset Allocation and Account Health:\n\n## 1. **Neural Network Visualization**\n- Asset allocation as glowing neural pathways connecting different asset nodes\n- Each asset type pulses with activity based on performance\n- Account health shown as a central \"brain\" core with radiating energy waves\n- Interactive: Click nodes to expand detailed holographic overlays\n\n## 2. **Holographic DNA Helix**\n- Asset allocation represented as a double helix structure\n- Each strand shows different asset classes (stocks, bonds, crypto)\n- Account health displayed as the helix's glow intensity and rotation speed\n- Risk level shown through color mutations (green=stable, red=volatile)\n\n## 3. **Quantum Particle Field**\n- Assets visualized as floating quantum particles in a 3D space\n- Particle size represents allocation percentage\n- Particle movement speed shows volatility/performance\n- Account health as an energy field containing the particles\n- Health bars replaced by particle density and field strength\n\nWhich concept excites you most? I can help implement any of these with modern web technologies.\n",
      "error": "",
      "returncode": 0
    }
  ]
}
