{
  "instruction": "We are moving to Phase 6: Auto-Execution. What are the critical safety checks and architectural patterns for implementing the 'Execute Trade' button safely? Also, list top 3 macro indicators to integrate.",
  "results": [
    {
      "model": "local/qwen",
      "executed": false,
      "output": "",
      "error": "Command 'qwen \"We are moving to Phase 6: Auto-Execution. What are the critical safety checks and architectural patterns for implementing the 'Execute Trade' button safely? Also, list top 3 macro indicators to integrate.\"' timed out after 120 seconds",
      "returncode": 0
    }
  ]
}
