{
  "instruction": "We are moving to Phase 8: Realtime Portfolio. We have raw trades in the DB. Design a robust 'PortfolioManager' class logic to calculate 'Total Equity', 'Cash', and 'Unrealized PnL' efficiently. How do we handle price updates?",
  "results": [
    {
      "model": "local/qwen",
      "executed": false,
      "output": "",
      "error": "Command 'qwen \"We are moving to Phase 8: Realtime Portfolio. We have raw trades in the DB. Design a robust 'PortfolioManager' class logic to calculate 'Total Equity', 'Cash', and 'Unrealized PnL' efficiently. How do we handle price updates?\"' timed out after 120 seconds",
      "returncode": 0
    }
  ]
}
