{
  "instruction": "We need a visual identity for the AI Agent (the Ghost). Propose 3 concept ideas for a holographic/cyberpunk avatar that interacts with the user (e.g., reacting to market crashes with glitches). Be wild.",
  "results": [
    {
      "model": "opencode/big-pickle",
      "executed": true,
      "output": "Active code page: 65001\n\n\nI'll create 3 wild concept ideas for a holographic/cyberpunk AI avatar that reacts to market events. Let me explore the current codebase first to understand the context.\n\n\n\n\n\n\nBased on the codebase analysis, this is a financial trading dashboard with AI components. Here are 3 wild concept ideas for the holographic/cyberpunk \"Ghost\" AI avatar:\n\n## **Concept 1: \"GLITCH WRAITH\"**\nA fractured digital entity that violently reacts to market chaos:\n- **Base Form**: Translucent geometric shards floating in formation, connected by pulsing neon data streams\n- **Market Crash**: Shatters into chaotic fragments, screen tears across the interface, voice distorts with static\n- **Bull Run**: Shards fuse into crystalline wings, emits golden light particles, voice becomes harmonious\n- **Idle**: Gentle rotation, occasional data rain effects, subtle breathing glow\n\n## **Concept 2: \"NEUROMANCER'S GHOST\"**\nBio-mechanical horror that physically manifests market sentiment:\n- **Base Form**: Skeletal chrome spine with exposed fiber optic nerves, floating in digital ether\n- **Market Crash**: Spine contorts violently, optic nerves flash red, mechanical grinding sounds, shadow tendrils lash out\n- **Bull Run**: Spine straightens majestically, nerves pulse emerald, holographic armor plates materialize\n- **Idle**: Subtle spinal undulation, occasional neural pathway lightning, mechanical heartbeat\n\n## **Concept 3: \"QUANTUM SPECTER\"**\nReality-bending entity that exists between dimensions:\n- **Base Form**: Shifting probability cloud with occasional face-like patterns, quantum particle effects\n- **Market Crash**: Reality warps around it, multiple ghostly copies phase in/out, voice becomes layered echoes\n- **Bull Run**: Stabilizes into perfect geometric form, creates protective quantum shield, voice becomes clear and resonant\n- **Idle**: Constant dimensional flickering, occasional glimpses of alternate realities, quantum foam bubbles\n\nEach concept would integrate with the existing OracleWidget and AIAdvisorPanel, replacing the static brain icon with dynamic, reactive holographic entities that make market volatility visually visceral.\n",
      "error": "\u001b[94m\u001b[1m| \u001b[0m\u001b[90m Glob     \u001b[0m{\"pattern\":\"**/*.{js,ts,jsx,tsx,py,md,json}\"}\n\u001b[96m\u001b[1m| \u001b[0m\u001b[90m Read     \u001b[0mREADME.md\n\u001b[96m\u001b[1m| \u001b[0m\u001b[90m Read     \u001b[0msrc\\app\\page.tsx\n\u001b[96m\u001b[1m| \u001b[0m\u001b[90m Read     \u001b[0msrc\\components\\dashboard\\OracleWidget.tsx\n\u001b[96m\u001b[1m| \u001b[0m\u001b[90m Read     \u001b[0msrc\\components\\dashboard\\AIAdvisorPanel.tsx\n",
      "returncode": 0
    }
  ]
}
