{
  "instruction": "We are about to perform a comprehensive source code review of the 'Ult' Trading System (Next.js + Python). What are the critical architectural, security, and performance pillars we must verify? List 5 strict technical commandments.",
  "results": [
    {
      "model": "local/qwen",
      "executed": true,
      "output": "Active code page: 65001\nI'll outline the critical architectural, security, and performance pillars for reviewing the 'Ult' Trading System. Since I'm in plan mode, I'll provide a comprehensive analysis without making any changes.\n\nHere are 5 strict technical commandments for the source code review:\n\n1. **Data Flow Integrity & Input Validation**: Verify all data inputs (market feeds, user inputs, API calls) are properly sanitized, validated, and sanitized at every entry point. Check for SQL injection, XSS vulnerabilities, and proper type checking in both Next.js frontend and Python backend.\n\n2. **Authentication & Authorization Security**: Examine the authentication mechanisms, session management, JWT handling, and role-based access controls. Ensure sensitive trading operations require proper authorization and that API endpoints are protected against unauthorized access.\n\n3. **Performance Under Load & Memory Management**: Review the system's ability to handle high-frequency trading data, concurrent users, and large datasets. Check for memory leaks, inefficient database queries, caching strategies, and proper resource cleanup in both JavaScript and Python components.\n\n4. **Financial Calculation Accuracy & Risk Management**: Validate all financial calculations, order processing logic, and risk management functions. Ensure precision in monetary calculations, proper handling of edge cases, and that the system implements appropriate safeguards against erroneous trades.\n\n5. **Audit Trail & Error Handling**: Verify comprehensive logging of all trading activities, system errors, and user actions. Ensure proper error handling that doesn't expose sensitive information while maintaining sufficient detail for debugging and compliance purposes.\n\nThese commandments form the foundation for a thorough security and performance review of the trading system.\n\nWould you like me to proceed with the detailed review following these commandments?\n",
      "error": "",
      "returncode": 0
    }
  ]
}
