{
  "instruction": "We are designing a 'System Health Monitor' dashboard. What key metrics (backend latency, DB connection pool, API rate limits) should be visualized to give a 'Spacecraft Cockpit' feel? Be technical.",
  "results": [
    {
      "model": "local/qwen",
      "executed": true,
      "output": "Active code page: 65001\nI'll help you design a System Health Monitor dashboard with a \"Spacecraft Cockpit\" feel, focusing on technical metrics that provide comprehensive system visibility. Let me create a plan for this.\n\n'll research'll research spacecraft cockpit design principles and key metrics hierarchy to inform our system health monitor design.\n\nSpacecraft cockpits are designed for mission-critical operations where pilots need instant awareness of all vital systems. The design principles include:\n\n1. **Critical-first hierarchy**: Most important metrics are most prominent and visible\n2. **Color-coded alerts**: Red for critical, yellow for warnings, green for normal operations\n3. **Real-time updates**: Continuous monitoring with immediate alerting\n4. **Redundant displays**: Multiple ways to see critical information\n5. **Minimal cognitive load**: Clear, unambiguous indicators that don't require interpretation\n6. **Grouped by system**: Related metrics grouped together (propulsion, navigation, life support, etc.)\n\nFor our System Health Monitor, we'll apply these principles by organizing metrics into logical groups with clear visual indicators.\n\nFor backend metrics, here are the critical indicators that should be visualized in a spacecraft cockpit-style dashboard:\n\n1. **Response Time Metrics**:\n   - P95/P99 Response Times (latency percentiles)\n   - Average Response Time\n   - Request Duration Distribution\n   - Slow Query Detection (>2s, >5s, >10s)\n\n2. **Throughput Metrics**:\n   - Requests Per Second (RPS)\n   - Operations Per Second\n   - Transaction Volume\n\n3. **Error Metrics**:\n   - Error Rate Percentage\n   - HTTP Status Code Breakdown (4xx, 5xx)\n   - Exception Count\n   - Failed Transaction Rate\n\n4. **Application Performance**:\n   - Active Connections\n   - Queue Length\n   - Thread Pool Utilization\n   - Garbage Collection Frequency/Duration (for JVM-based systems)\n\n5. **Business Logic Metrics**:\n   - Key Business Transaction Success Rates\n   - Feature-Specific Performance Indicators\n\nThese metrics should be displayed with clear thresholds and color-coded alerts to indicate normal, warning, and critical states.\n\nFor database health indicators, here are the critical metrics that should be monitored in a spacecraft cockpit-style dashboard:\n\n1. **Connection Metrics**:\n   - Active Connections vs Max Pool Size\n   - Connection Pool Utilization %\n   - Idle Connections\n   - Connection Wait Time\n   - Failed Connection Attempts\n\n2. **Performance Metrics**:\n   - Query Response Times (P95/P99)\n   - Slow Query Count (>1s, >5s)\n   - Deadlock Detection\n   - Lock Waits and Contention\n\n3. **Resource Utilization**:\n   - Database CPU Usage\n   - Memory Usage\n   - Disk I/O Operations\n   - Buffer Cache Hit Ratio\n\n4. **Replication Metrics** (for clustered databases):\n   - Replication Lag\n   - Slave/Secondary Sync Status\n   - Failover Events\n\n5. **Storage Metrics**:\n   - Disk Space Usage\n   - Table Growth Rate\n   - Index Fragmentation\n\n6. **Transaction Metrics**:\n   - Transactions Per Second\n   - Rollback Rate\n   - Active Long-Running Transactions\n\nThese metrics should be visualized with clear thresholds indicating healthy, warning, and critical states, similar to how fuel levels, oxygen, and power systems would be monitored in a spacecraft.\n\nFor API rate limiting and traffic metrics, here are the key indicators that should be visualized in a spacecraft cockpit-style dashboard:\n\n1. **Rate Limiting Metrics**:\n   - Current API Usage vs Limits (% of quota)\n   - Rate Limit Exceeded Events\n   - Throttled Request Count\n   - Remaining Quota Display\n   - Burst vs Sustained Traffic Patterns\n\n2. **Traffic Metrics**:\n   - Requests Per Minute/Hour\n   - Concurrent Active Requests\n   - Traffic Distribution by Endpoint\n   - Geographic Request Distribution\n   - Traffic Spikes Detection\n\n3. **Client-Specific Metrics**:\n   - Top Consumers by Request Volume\n   - Individual Client Rate Limit Status\n   - Unauthorized/Bad Request Counts\n   - Client-Specific Error Rates\n\n4. **API Gateway Metrics**:\n   - Load Balancer Health\n   - Circuit Breaker Status\n   - Failover Events\n   - SSL/TLS Handshake Success Rate\n\n5. **Compliance and Security**:\n   - Suspicious Request Patterns\n   - DDoS Attack Detection Indicators\n   - Authentication Failure Rates\n\nThese metrics should be displayed with clear visual indicators showing when limits are approaching, being reached, or exceeded, similar to how fuel consumption and remaining capacity would be monitored during a space mission.\n\nFor infrastructure and resource metrics, here are the critical indicators that should be included in a spacecraft cockpit-style dashboard:\n\n1. **Compute Resources**:\n   - CPU Utilization % (with critical thresholds)\n   - CPU Load Average\n   - Memory Usage % (RAM)\n   - Swap Usage\n   - Process Count\n   - Container Resource Limits (if using containers)\n\n2. **Storage Metrics**:\n   - Disk Usage % (by volume/mount point)\n   - Disk I/O Operations Per Second\n   - Storage Throughput (Read/Write MB/s)\n   - Available Inode Count\n   - Disk Latency\n\n3. **Network Metrics**:\n   - Bandwidth Utilization (Inbound/Outbound)\n   - Network Errors/Drop Rate\n   - Packet Loss %\n   - Network Latency/Jitter\n   - Active Network Connections\n\n4. **Infrastructure Health**:\n   - Server Uptime\n   - Health Check Status\n   - Service Availability %\n   - Node Status (in cluster environments)\n   - Auto-scaling Events\n\n5. **Environmental Metrics** (if applicable):\n   - Temperature Sensors (for physical hardware)\n   - Power Supply Status\n   - Fan Speed/RPM\n\n6. **Cloud-Specific Metrics** (if using cloud infrastructure):\n   - Instance Health Status\n   - Load Balancer Metrics\n   - CDN Performance\n   - Cloud Service Availability\n\nThese metrics form the foundation of system health, similar to how environmental controls, power systems, and structural integrity are monitored in spacecraft.\n\nFor the visual hierarchy of a cockpit-style interface, here's the recommended design approach:\n\n1. **Primary Flight Display (PFD) Equivalent** - Critical System Status:\n   - Overall System Health Score (0-100%)\n   - Current Alert Level (Normal/Warning/Critical)\n   - Uptime/Availability Indicator\n   - Major Incident Status\n\n2. **Navigation Display (ND) Equivalent** - Traffic & Flow:\n   - Real-time Request Volume Graph\n   - API Rate Limit Status (dials showing % of quota used)\n   - Geographic Traffic Distribution Map\n\n3. **Engine Indicators (EICAS/ECAM) Equivalent** - Backend & Infrastructure:\n   - CPU/Memory/Storage Gauges (analog dials with red/yellow/green zones)\n   - Response Time Histograms\n   - Error Rate Indicators\n   - Active Connections Counter\n\n4. **Warning Panel** - Alerts & Notifications:\n   - Flashing lights for critical issues\n   - Alert Priority Queue\n   - Acknowledged vs Unacknowledged Alarms\n   - Escalation Timers\n\n5. **Secondary Displays** - Detailed Metrics:\n   - Database Connection Pool Status\n   - Slow Query Detection\n   - Individual Service Health\n   - Historical Trend Charts\n\n6. **Visual Design Elements**:\n   - Dark background with high-contrast text (reduces eye strain during long monitoring sessions)\n   - Consistent color coding: Green (normal), Yellow (warning), Red (critical), Blue (information)\n   - Analog gauges for continuous metrics, digital readouts for discrete values\n   - Minimal text, maximum visual information density\n   - Consistent positioning: critical metrics in upper center, supporting metrics around periphery\n\nThis design ensures operators can quickly assess system status at a glance, similar to how astronauts monitor spacecraft systems during critical operations.\n\n on my on my research and analysis, I've completed the planning for your System Health Monitor dashboard with a \"Spacecraft Cockpit\" feel. Here's the comprehensive plan:\n\n## System Health Monitor - Spacecraft Cockpit Dashboard\n\n### Key Metric Categories:\n\n1. **Backend Performance Metrics**:\n   - P95/P99 Response Times\n   - Requests Per Second\n   - Error Rate Percentage\n   - Thread Pool Utilization\n   - Active Connections\n\n2. **Database Health Indicators**:\n   - Connection Pool Utilization %\n   - Query Response Times\n   - Database CPU/Memory Usage\n   - Replication Lag\n   - Transaction Rates\n\n3. **API Rate Limiting & Traffic**:\n   - Current Usage vs Limits (% of quota)\n   - Rate Limit Exceeded Events\n   - Requests Per Minute/Hour\n   - Client-Specific Limits Status\n\n4. **Infrastructure & Resource Metrics**:\n   - CPU/Memory/Disk Utilization\n   - Network Bandwidth & Latency\n   - Server Uptime\n   - Container Resource Limits\n\n### Visual Hierarchy Design:\n- **Primary Display**: Overall system health score and alert level\n- **Traffic Flow Section**: Real-time request volume and geographic distribution\n- **Engine Indicators**: Resource utilization gauges with color-coded zones\n- **Warning Panel**: Critical alerts with flashing indicators\n- **Detailed Metrics**: Secondary displays for in-depth analysis\n\nThe design follows spacecraft cockpit principles with dark backgrounds, high contrast, consistent color coding (green/yellow/red), analog gauges for continuous metrics, and minimal text for maximum information density.\n\nWould you like me to proceed with implementing this dashboard design?\n",
      "error": "",
      "returncode": 0
    }
  ]
}
