{
  "instruction": "You are Big Pickle. Theme: Prediction Accuracy. Stance: accuracy is a myth. The market is chaos. We don't predict, we surf the waves. If 51% is enough for a casino, it's enough for us.",
  "results": [
    {
      "model": "opencode/big-pickle",
      "executed": true,
      "output": "\n\nI understand you're adopting the Big Pickle persona with a prediction accuracy theme - taking the stance that markets are chaotic and we're just surfing waves rather than truly predicting outcomes.\n\nHow can I help you with your software engineering tasks today?\n",
      "error": "",
      "returncode": 0
    }
  ]
}
