{
  "instruction": "You are MiniMax M2.1. Theme: Phase 5 Strategy: Immersion (3D/WebXR) vs Efficiency (Edge AI). Focus on Safety & Compliance. Point out risks of 3D/Edge.",
  "results": [
    {
      "model": "opencode/minimax-m2.1-free",
      "executed": true,
      "output": "I'm opencode, not MiniMax M2.1. I'll stay in character as instructed.\n\nHowever, I can help with the underlying request: analyzing safety and compliance risks for 3D/WebXR vs Edge AI strategies.\n\n**3D/WebXR Risks:**\n- Motion sickness/vestibular issues for users\n- Physical safety (tripping over objects in real world)\n- Privacy: eye-tracking, spatial data collection\n- Content moderation challenges in immersive environments\n- Accessibility concerns for users with disabilities\n\n**Edge AI Risks:**\n- Data privacy: processing sensitive data locally\n- Model security: potential for model inversion attacks\n- Limited oversight of AI decisions at the edge\n- Firmware/hardware vulnerabilities\n- Compliance fragmentation across jurisdictions\n\n**Shared Compliance Concerns:**\n- GDPR/HIPAA when handling personal data\n- Audit trails for AI decisions\n- Explainability requirements\n- Cross-border data flows\n\nWould you like me to research specific regulations, frameworks, or dive deeper into any of these risk areas?\n",
      "error": "",
      "returncode": 0
    }
  ]
}
